{"classes":["ORG","PER","LOCATION","PRODUCTS","DATE & TIME","MONEY","PERCENTAGE","RATIO","VOLUME","CORPORATE ACTIONS","MARKET EVENTS","POSITIVE","NEGATIVE","EQUITIES","BONDS","REGULATIONS","OTHER"],"annotations":[["Description\r",{"entities":[]}],["Piramal, Tata Power, and TVS group units figure in list\r",{"entities":[[0,7,"ORG"],[9,19,"ORG"],[25,34,"ORG"]]}],["With no upper limit, interest rates in this sphere can go as high as 35 per cent. However, even with high interest rates, many ...\r",{"entities":[[69,81,"PERCENTAGE"]]}],["The forward premium comes down when the demand for the spot is more than the future dollar\r",{"entities":[[4,19,"MARKET EVENTS"]]}],["Among all banks, SBI controls a market share of 22% in the MSME lending\r",{"entities":[[17,20,"ORG"],[48,51,"PERCENTAGE"],[59,63,"ORG"],[64,71,"PRODUCTS"]]}],["Currency in circulation (CIC), in the fortnight ended April 10 stood at Rs 49,554.30 crore\r",{"entities":[[0,29,"MONEY"],[54,62,"DATE & TIME"],[72,90,"MONEY"]]}],["Reluctant to lend to NBFCs, MFIs in current situation\r",{"entities":[[21,26,"ORG"],[28,32,"ORG"]]}],["The finance ministry, in a letter dated April 17 and seen by Reuters, asked banks to furnish detailed data on new loans, ...\r",{"entities":[[4,20,"ORG"],[40,48,"DATE & TIME"],[61,68,"ORG"],[114,119,"PRODUCTS"]]}],["Five small finance banks, including Equitas SFB, are due for listing by 2021\r",{"entities":[[36,47,"ORG"],[61,68,"CORPORATE ACTIONS"]]}],["The latest auction was part of the TLTRO 2.0, through which RBI had planned to infuse up to Rs 50,000 crore, to begin with.\r",{"entities":[[11,18,"MARKET EVENTS"],[35,44,"OTHER"],[60,63,"ORG"],[92,107,"MONEY"]]}],["Credit enhancement would entail guarantee from bigger institutions in case of defaults up to a certain percentage\r",{"entities":[[0,18,"OTHER"]]}],["NBFCs and MFIs have been hit on two fronts, with collections dipping due to the covid-19 lockdown, and the three-month moratorium ...\r",{"entities":[[0,5,"ORG"],[10,14,"ORG"],[25,28,"NEGATIVE"],[61,68,"NEGATIVE"],[119,129,"REGULATIONS"]]}],["According to the latest available figures, the Reserve Bank of India had about Rs 9 trillion worth of bonds on its books\r",{"entities":[[47,68,"ORG"],[79,92,"MONEY"],[102,107,"BONDS"]]}],["Use instalments to increase cover; benefit from quick approvals\r",{"entities":[[4,15,"PRODUCTS"]]}],["We need to understand the nature of the astronomical tax arrears' figure of Rs 9 trillion\r",{"entities":[[53,64,"REGULATIONS"],[76,89,"MONEY"]]}],["'The burden of unsold inventory of over half a million housing units in the top 7 cities will worsen due to impact of the ...\r",{"entities":[[94,100,"NEGATIVE"]]}],["Even after the Reserve Bank of India 'permitted' banks to offer a three-month moratorium to borrowers (of all hues), NBFCs ...\r",{"entities":[[15,36,"ORG"],[78,88,"REGULATIONS"],[117,122,"ORG"]]}],["Many farmers couldn't visit banks to pay dues on short-term crop loans in the wake of the Covid-19 lockdown and restrictions on ...\r",{"entities":[[65,70,"PRODUCTS"]]}],["Banks want tenants to make payment in escrow accounts\r",{"entities":[[38,53,"OTHER"]]}],["The reduction in rate comes after the RBI provided a boost to the banking system through its policy measures and also introduced ...\r",{"entities":[[38,41,"ORG"]]}],["The extension has been granted based on the feedback received from banks and taking into account the disruptions caused by ...\r",{"entities":[[101,112,"NEGATIVE"]]}],["The Bank did not elaborate the extent of its exposure and the steps it is taking to protect its interest\r",{"entities":[]}],["It now holds 72 million shares in the lender\r",{"entities":[[13,30,"EQUITIES"]]}],["Asia's banking sector profitability will also decline from deteriorating asset quality and lower net interest margins, said ...\r",{"entities":[[0,4,"LOCATION"],[46,53,"NEGATIVE"],[59,72,"NEGATIVE"]]}],["The tankers, Wu Yi San and Chang Bai San, were carrying cargoes financed by ICICI, the source said, adding the bank had about ...\r",{"entities":[[13,22,"PER"],[27,40,"PER"],[76,81,"ORG"]]}],["The RBI has so far not provided any clarity on whether banks will grant moratorium to the shadow lenders on the loans they have ...\r",{"entities":[[4,7,"ORG"],[72,82,"REGULATIONS"],[90,104,"OTHER"],[112,117,"PRODUCTS"]]}],["",{"entities":[]}]]}